Intro:|D#m|D#m|D#m|D#m|

                D#m
1.This is the last time you say
           C#
After the last line you break
         Bm
It's not even a holiday
               H
Nothing to celebrate
You give a hundred reasons why
And say you really gonna try
If i had a nickle for everytime
I'd own the bank

Thought that I was the exception
I could re-write your addiction
You could have been the greatest
But you rather get wasted

Chorus:
     D#m
You fall asleep and during foreplay
           H
Cause the pills you take are more your forté
 G                  F#               H      E
I'm not sticking around to watch you go down
Wanna be your lover, not your fuckin' mother
Can't be your saviour, I don't have the power
I'm not gonna stay and watch you circle the drain, watch you circle the drain
                      D#m
Watch you circle the drain.

Interlude:|D#m|D#m|

2.You say it helps you write your rimes,
Whatever helps you sleep at night
You become what you despise
A stereo-type
You think you're so rock'n'roll
But you're really just a joke
Had the world in the palm of your hands
But you fuckin' choked

Should have been my teenmate
Could've change your faith
You said that you love me
You won't remember in the morning

Chorus.

Interlude:|D#m|D#m|D#m|D#m|

Chorus.

 D#m
Watch you circle the drain... Watch you circle the drain
  D#m                          H
Nananana nana na bam - bam, Darararararara - Bam - Bam,
 G                  F#                   H                E
You're going down, you're going down, you're going down, You're goin ...
      D#m
You fall asleep and during foreplay
              C#
Because the pills you take are more your forté
  Bm                                   H      E
I'm not stickin' around to watch you go down...